<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<book>
    <page>
        <text>
            Chapter 1
            I shifted my weight and then shifted again, as if finding the perfect posture would make me feel comfortable. Ded Pimpin and I were breaking out of game jail. It’d been 80 years since the Fed revolutionized the incarceration industry with a progressive cocktail of cryonics and brain-machine interfaces. They made it sound more like college.

            I still had the same feeling of nausea that came up when I was booked. I’d seen the nurse about it a million times. She assured me that my brain-scanned mind and body-scanned avatar would conjoin, and the nausea would subside. Every so often, my cryogenically frozen body is thawed and updated with my experiences in jail. I never did figure out if that type of update went two-ways. For example, if I was scanned during a panic attack, was that the baseline for my avatar? {testing}

            Watching Ded infect game jail with malware was satisfying. It was as if game jail finally felt the unease that I’d been suffering all along. World-class artists had been commissioned to design several aspects of the Platinum Digital Penitentiary Experience: evolving the mind, protecting the body. The geographic setting was modeled off the Jordan River basin. Walking in the +x direction along the river, olive trees glimmered along crystalline limestone alternated with shale. The next layers up were gypsum, iron-rich stone, and fossil-rich sandstone. Forests of wild oak grew on the hillsides. Herds of gazelles drank along side flocks of storks and larks. Inmates settled along the banks and cultivated fruit orchards and vegetable fields. Prehistoric creatures flew around teaching us philosophy, law, language – whatever we wanted. Completing the biblical concept, all creatures glowed with auras that broadcast internal states of health and emotion. 

            The reality of game jail was surely based on faith. There was no "external display" to share with "others." My experience was rendered within the visual cortex of the scanned copy of my brain – for efficiency, of course. The multiplayer element was impossible to confirm... until now? 

            Standing on the massive rock formation marking the origin, Ded Pimpin had been spewing viral code for 10M frames. She’d been suppressing the virus as a hidden component to let it build up. Eventually, the virus infected every variable and function attached to her avatar. Suppression became a constant, conscious effort, especially since no one hated game jail more than Ded. Now her aura billowed with the manic primacy of long-awaited retaliation. If this wasn’t proof of existence, I don’t know what was. 

            For all the artistry invested in this mental space, the infection seemed to complete it. The virus shot from Ded’s mouth in white pellets. These pellets took root like seeds. Shiny, slug-like vines exploded and stuck to the terrain. Along each tendril, a rash of suction cups gorged. Each slowly birthed a straw that drilled an irrigation system. Flora reacted first. To my right, an apple tree writhed like a maced dinosaur. Olive tree auras smoked up in the +y, charring spots of goo into the skybox. Slug vines piled up like foam on the shore. Frenetic fish jumped out of the river and bizarrely twitched through the air. 

            The birds were screaming. Intending to enhance inmate sensitivity and decrease privacy, everyone could hear over an infinite distance in game jail. Normally this wasn’t an issue. But the cacophony betrayed that there was no buffer to mitigate the deafening cries of panic. 

            Ester hopped in front of me. Ester was a bunny that the inmates had constructed out of polygons as an art-therapy project. Maybe Ester would be spared. Such were the perks of non-existence. When I reached out my hand to pet her nose, she straight up exploded. 

            Being deadly is a funny thing. You’d think it’d be more exciting. Over the white shards of bunny, I studied my viral-shedding palm. 

            When Ded Pimpin first took me to the beach and traced blueprints of our escape in the sand, I could have gone either way. There wasn’t much for me out there. It was only in the process of interacting with her physically in order to transmit the damn thing that I became interested in her. I guess you could call our love making vaccination. The intimacy was a strategy to control the spread of the virus. We wanted to build up enough antibodies to protect us from the outbreak. Beautifully, controlling the virus was initially a matter of willpower. Now the environmental levels were so high, my presence had more impact. 

            Game jail looked like inside of a corroding battery. The swan songs were quieting down. Airborne agents braised the skybox with bubbling suppressants. I was so overwhelmed that I yawned. 

            "Do you want to die?" Ded croaked in her apathetic, stoner drawl. 

            Whether she meant by the hand of agents, the virus, or by her own hand, I couldn’t be sure. 

            "No," I decided. 

            Her skin texture was stretched and puffy from the expulsion. Her aura was a grey wad of sludge – not healthy. Now came for my role. I hoisted her wan frame over my shoulders. I was already loaded with the shields, but it felt like she’d dropped some weight in the shedding. Maybe the gravity parameter was bugging out. As I sprinted her do -z over fields of jiggling rancidity, I wondered how it’d been painful for her to hide the virus for so long. There were so many types of pain. 

        </text>
    </page>

    <page>
        <text>

            Chapter 2
            We reached the ocean. Ded was still shedding pellets orally, leaving behind a trail of tumors radially sprouting tendrils. The setting sun cast an orange glow on viral plumes eating through helicops and palm trees marching down the -z peninsula. This was where the prison palace ended and the container program began. Two-point-high waves - twice the height of the tallest avatar - crashed against the shore. No one surfed these waters though. The waves were generated. The liquid surrounded the penitentiary with a moat filled with acid and jumbo piranhas. Swimming would dissolve any non-viral cells in our bodies. The piranhas theoretically could eat us, but our viral cells would burn through them too. 

            Our plan was to use the infection to trigger a program exit, which would restore our "souls" to our physiological neurons on the outside. A proper ejection was ideal, otherwise we could wake up retarded, epileptic, senile, or psychopathic. However, the program won’t eject perpetrators. Before the program exit, we had to reach the container program and muck with our file structures. 

            We’d diverted agent attacks thus far with my shields, but they’d melt in the moat. At that point, agent signals could infiltrate our minds and immobilize us. 

            Our task was to cross the moat while we still had limbs enough to swim. The acidifying water emitted putrid vapor. I pulled out the palliative shot.

            "Last chance."

            Ded’s eyes drooped and her mouth spread open with that surprisingly large smile of hers – slightly embarrassed, but disarmingly well structured. 

            "I mean I’m down if you are." Ded was always down to get high. 

            "Can we afford the side effects?"

            Ded thought for a moment. 

            Agents swarmed above us. Of course they knew where we were, but they couldn’t get in until they’d disarmed the shields. Their fleet was greatly compromised by the infection. Every so often, another one dropped from the skybox. But I could already feel the shields loosening. Agent signals were entering my consciousness. It felt like self-doubt. The problem was, with the painkillers, we might loose track of the difference between us and them. 

            "No I don’t think so," Ded sighed.

            As we waded in, a buttery fish glided through my leg and surfaced as a bisected skeleton. Even though my flesh was burning off, I felt the pain most intensely in my abdomen. Initially, I crapped and puked, but soon my tissue was too worn to do that. Our screams deadened to dull rasps through our opened throats. We clicked with frame drops as the program processed the war between our viral cells and the acid. 

            By about five points from shore, we settled into a brisk stroke. The erosion of our bodies slowed as the acid up against the areas where the virus had most deeply taken hold: bone, connective tissue, in some areas muscle. Anything above water was pretty near in tact. Just a few points away, I could make out the container’s edge. There was a distinct resolution drop drawn over the acid like a curtain. It looked a bit like "God rays" after a storm. The container’s side was brighter and more difficult to hold in focus. 

            "Where’s the buoy?" I scanned the edge. 

            "I don’t. Fucking. See it."

            These utterances were literally gurgles of blood and acid. 

            Our blueprints indicated one entrance to the container program: a large, green rubber ducky. The agents swarmed like bees, overloading my ears and obstructing my view. 

            "Maybe it sank?" I ducked under the water to check. Below, piranhas nipped at my legs with melting mouths. The acid wreaked havoc on my virgin head. Luckily the eyes were a viral hotpot, so they remained. Through a film of neutralizing acid, I saw the glowing form of the ducky. Suddenly the edge flickered. 

            I surfaced. 

            "That way," but nothing came out. From the look on Ded’s face, mine was gone. The curtain glitched again. 

            "If they lock it… Soma." Ded grasped my hand in an uncharacteristic show of need. I saw glittering fractals in the lines on her face. Her eyes dilated. The barrettes melted like streamers in her hair, which fell out in clumps. I thought of cancer.

            "Baby," she whined.

            I was having a spell. Fear gripped me now. I was going to die here. I’d imagined that death in game jail would feel like slipping on a banana peel: cliché in the best way. But in practice, the sense of doom was paralyzing. 

            Ded was swimming away from me now. She would. A missile flew towards her. They’ve resorted to weakening us manually. I was sinking slowly. Or quickly. Ded was swimming away from me. I saw her growing smaller in my eye. I should tell her about the missile. She didn’t see it. I swam to Ded. 

            Muscle slid off her bones in chunks. I clawed my way up her skeleton and grabbed her smoking cervical vertebrae. Twisting her head, I kissed her melting lips. Our jaw bones ground against each other. Teeth and tongue tissue improvised. 

            Directly behind, the missile entered the water. Its vacuum sucked us under, past the green ducky, past the edge of game jail. 

            The temperature dropped. We slid on the cheap linoleum floor of a long hallway. This must be where the plants take their breaks – like those tunnels under Disneyland. It was dark. Or maybe I was going blind. A faint beeping came from a red blur beside us. 
             
            My skeletal digits were knotted in Ded’s ratty hair. I wasn’t done with her.  

            As I carried out my business of living, the missile detonated. 

        </text>
    </page>
</book>